const todosData = [
    {
        id: 1,
        person : "James",
        question : "Which NBA team does James support?",
        options: ["Rockets","OKC","Lakers"],
        answer:"Lakers",
        img: ""
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        person : "Sitggen",
        question : "Which university did Sitggen study at?",
        options: ["Melbourne Uni","Monash","RMIT"],
        answer:"Monash",
        img: ""
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        person : "Will",
        question : "What did Will's boss ask him to do on his first day as a graduate?",
        options: ["Go home","Buy everyone donuts","Polish his shoes"],
        answer:"Polish his shoes",
        img: ""
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        person : "Thanh",
        question : "What kind of tree does Thanh have in her backyard?",
        options: ["Lemon","Orange","Gooseberry"],
        answer:"Lemon",
        img: ""
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        person : "Andrew",
        question : "Which of the following is Andrew allergic to?",
        options: ["Nuts","Milk","Fish"],
        answer:"Milk",
        img: ""
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        person : "Haris",
        question : "Where is Haris's favourite curry place?",
        options: ["Ziyka","Ajisen","Curry House"],
        answer:"Ajisen",
        img: ""
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        person : "Stephan",
        question : "How many cats does Stephan have?",
        options: ["3","4","2"],
        answer:"4",
        img: ""
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        person : "Soheb",
        question : "What is Soheb's role at Telstra?",
        options: ["UI/UX","Scrum Master","Provider of sweets","All 3 options"],
        answer:"All 3 options",
        img: ""
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        person : "Alison",
        question : "Which one of these places has Alison previously worked at?",
        options: ["Isreal","Malaysia","Russia"],
        answer:"Isreal",
        img: ""
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        person : "Chris T",
        question : "How many years will Chris T usually spend in a team?",
        options: ["3","4","5"],
        answer:"4",
        img: ""
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        person : "Chris M",
        question : "Which of these is Chris M's favourite food?",
        options: ["Curry","Pizza","Kebabs"],
        answer:"Curry",
        img: ""
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        person : "Jovi",
        question : "Has Jovi ever beaten Andrew in basketball?",
        options: ["Yes","No"],
        answer:"Yes",
        img: ""
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        person : "Mike",
        question : "Which of these places does Mike shop at?",
        options: ["Woolies","Costco","Coles"],
        answer:"Coles",
        img: ""
    }
]

export default todosData